

○ Vladimir, Brajshe, Ulqin, 85360, Montenegro

+38267631921, +355674828297, +38268069921

Profile

I am an enthusiastic and passionate developer/programmer who loves to write code, solve problems, automate stuff, and build websites & softwares. Experienced with the latest cutting edge development tools and procedures. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team. I'm always looking forward to learn new skills and add them in the list.

Work Experience

Full Stack Developer, Landmark Technologies, Tirana

September 2021 — Present

- Reactjs in the front and Nestjs in the back, with Typescript.
- Fully engaged with team members to achieve the highest levels of productivity, to build an Multi Role based LMS and Online Course Provider.
- ANTd and Styled Components for design implementation, Redux for state management, Paypal for payment processing, Reacti18next for multi language application, Formik and yup etc.
- Created custom reusable components and hooks.

Senior Reactjs Developer, Icon Group - Icon Mobile, Berlin

January 2022 — February 2022

Worked on a short term project, on which the general idea was about Heating Value Optimization, creating graphs of the real data and also data after being optimized.

- The main technologies that I used on this project were: Reactjs for the UI, Redux for global state management - in case the project grows with time, and D3.js for chart creation.
- Implemented and updated application modules under the direction of Senior Software Developers.
- Worked to support the senior creative staff with day-to-day tasks.
- Documented all concerns and incidents and reported them to a senior supervisor.

Full Stack, MERN Stack Developer, Cartys, Freelance, Part Time

January 2021 — September 2021

- Worked well independently and on a team to solve problems.
- Organized and prioritized work to complete assignments in a timely, efficient
- React Native with Expo to create Native Application, React Navigation v5, etc.
- Build re-usable components using Touchables control components and Flatlists
- Create a SPA with React and Material-UI, and Redux as a state management.
- Wrote custom hooks to get user auth object and other common pieces of data from Redux state.

Details

Date of birth

24/01/1997

Skills

HTML

CSS

Scss

JavaScript

React

Node.js

Express.js

MongoDB

React Native

Gatsby

Next.js

.

MySQL

Links

<u>Facebook</u>

Instagram

Twitter

Linked In

<u>Github</u>

Hobbies

Football, Swimimng, Tennis

Languages

- jasminluka007@gmail.com
 - Build a component which takes care of pushed layout on keyboard hide which also renders children
 - Stripe as payment gateway and Timekit.io for scheduling.
 - Integration with RESTful API.
 - A customer of a specific user store, can view their bookings, upcoming and history of schedules, buy and schedule new sessions for specific event.
 - Create a fully functional server with Authentication Register, Login, Forgot Password etc, Push Notifications and Stripe Treasury

Frontend, React Developer, Flex Business Solutions, Tirana

March 2021 — August 2021

- Served as a friendly, hardworking, and punctual employee.
- Fully engaged with team members to achieve the highest levels of productivity, to build an Multi Role based CRM App using React, and AWS Amplify.
- Material-UI and ANTd for design implementation, Redux for state management, WebSockets, AgGrid for data grid, Google API for Google Maps, And Google Drive.
- Created custom reusable components and hooks, Implemented logic to create Schedule of Values similar to Quick Books, and export to CSV and PDF.

Frontend Developer, React, Turistic Agency, Ulgin

January 2019 — December 2020

Added features to ReactJs Web App, and maintained the web site of company.

Personal Projects

February 2016 — Present

- 1. Fondacioni Deshmia. A Donation App, created with MERN Stack and Stripe as a payment gateway for a single donation or monthly subscription. It has a Role based system where only Admin or Publisher can add new causes and news and update or delete them. Admin can approve other registered user to have status of a Publisher.
- 2. Social Media App. Built on MERN Stack. It includes authentication, profile and forum posts, with likes and comments functionality.
- 3. API for a Boot camp. Back end API created with Express and MongoDB for the Camp application to manage boot camps, courses, reviews, users and authentication.
- 4. Pizza Ordering System. A system created with React on the front, Express and MongoDB on server side. It is a Role based System (Admin and User), where the Admin creates menu and reviews orders made by users. Users can make orders as a guest or as a registered user which enables them to view their history of orders.
- 5. Reddit clone. Cloning Reddit with Next.js and Tailwind as front end frameworks, and Express, PostgreSQL and TypeOrm on the server side.
- 6. A Portfolio for a graphic designer & photo-shooter. Created with HTML, SCSS and JavaScript.
- 7. GitHub Account. Authenticate to GitHub and list repositories of your account or search for other user accounts.
- 8. Notebook App. Created with MERN Stack, Has CRUD functionality for notes and ability to categorize notes, it also has efficient search with debounce implemented.



9. Blog Page. A JAM stack Created with Gatsby.js, GraphQL and MarkDown. Create blogs with MarkDown and fetch and show to UI with Gatsby & GraphQL.

Education

Master of Science, Computer Engineering, Epoka University, Tirana

October 2017 — September 2019

Bachelor, Computer Engineering, Epoka University, Tirana

October 2014 — July 2017

High School, Hasan Riza Pasha College, Shkodër

September 2011 — July 2014

Primary, Bedri Elezaga, Ulqin

September 2003 — June 2011

Internships

Assistant, Epoka Ulniversity, Tirana

November 2016 — March 2017

• Assisted in Lab Hours of Introduction to Algorithms and C++ Course.

Intern at ALBtelecom & Eagle Mobile, Tirana

June 2016 — July 2016